The distant future
Vampires rule the night, but their numbers are dwindling
With huge bounties on their heads, a class of hunters has emerged, Bounty Hunters
One hunter is unlike all the others He is a Dunpeal; a half human half vampire
At war with himself, feared by all, tortured and alone, he is
Here he comes!
Hail Mary, full of grace The Lord is with thee Blessed art thou among women Blessed is the Lord Jesus Christ
We've been expecting you
I'm Alan Elbourne, and I'm the one that summoned you here today for this reason
Go on I'm listening
It's about my sister, Charlotte
Two nights ago she disappeared
She was in bed, sleeping; it was the middle of the night
Several people told us they saw a carriage outside our house
The carriage
belonged to Meier Link, the vampire
I organized a search party of fifty men
but it was no use; we couldn't find them
We were ambushed
took my sister and killed my friends
That's just a down payment
You'll get the rest when you find her
Ten million dollars
But you better move fast
you've got some competition
I've hired the Markus Brothers
and they've got a head start on you
I don't think so
Huh?
It may be too late for her
Your sister may already have been tempted
What then?
You have to get there before that happens
what do you think we're paying you for?!
That's enough!
My son is emotional; please excuse him
This has been difficult for all of us
If you knew my daughter, you'd understand
she's kind and beautiful
and her loss is more than this old soul can bear
Now, I need to ask you something
if you find her changed, can you see that her death is without suffering
Be kind to her, please
No -no!
We can't do that; it isn't right
No! She won't be changed
you're talking about your daughter!
Alan, listen to me
It's not easy to ask him for this
but it's something that must be done
I'm sorry
Do you understand?
I understand your position, but
ten million dollars is not enough
What?
How dare you!
Stop it
hold your fire!
I said stop!
I'll double the price
I'll give you twenty million
Just bring her back
one way or the other
Did you see a carriage go by here with four horses in front?
Let me go
let me go
le
You're lying
Oh, damn; we got company
Lotsa company
Look out!
Oh, man Is everybody OK?
Yeah
Do you believe that?
The place is overrun with them
He musta been here already
Well, c'mon
ready or not, here they come
It's zombie time
Yeah, come and get it, zombies!
Amen to that
Leila, are you there?
It won't take long, Grove
Juststay in the tank
Can't load!
Not so fast, buddy
And
fire!
Gotcha!
Rest in peace, huh?
You hear that?
Sounds like a horse
It's movinguphill
Let me try
Right
right about
right there!
Beautiful, just beautiful
I applaud you, stranger
Tell me what you're doing here
If we're in the same game, we should be friends
Tell me your name
Mine's Borgoff, Borgoff Markus
D
Ah, so that's the guy, the dhampir hunter
I've heard about him
He's amazing
Wake up, Borgoff, he's the competition, not some buddy of ours
C'mon, what are we doing here, we just helped him, think about it
Yeah, he's right, I agree with him about that
We help him too much and he'll take all the money
If it wasn't for us, he'd be dead by now
We do the work and he gets the reward
Ah, you boys should relax
We just did the famous dhampir a little favor is all
A little favor we can't afford
Hey
y'ever hear the one about the owl and squirrel?
Squirrel works all summer storin' away stuff for the winter, all kinds of nuts and seeds
works real hard
Then one day just before the first snow he goes outside for one last look around when
all of a sudden this owl swoops down and
grabs him, carries him off
"Ah, what a shame," says the squirrel
"'cause what's gonna happen to all that good food?"
Aw, that's a good one
Yeah, hilarious
You get it, you guys?
That stupid squirrel is all I can
Leila!
Hey, Leila, what's the rush?
What's with her?
So you're outnumbered, four to one; so what?
They do have a head start, but when the sun comes up, the heat will slow 'em down
Speaking of, ah, sun and heat, I know I don't need to remind you of your susceptibility
It's called heat syndrome
and the last time you ignored it, you almost
Don't worry
I hate it when you say that
Whatwhat are those ?
Tracks
let me see
Yes, OK! these are definitely that tracks, six hours old I'd say
OK
I'm suffocating now
Hey, how was that?
That's funny
I could have sworn I heard something
Quiet
Sand mantas, most likely
Sweet blasphemy, sand mantas galore!
Talk about your prehistoric pigeons
They're filthy animals, y'know, they're just filthy!
Well, I--I guess we better just turn back
it's a shame, really, 'cause you know, we could
No -go back, man
go back, now, c'mon
you're crazy
c'mon, man -please, let's' just go back
That -that was good
OK, now, we survived that, could we stop?
Diddid you ever hear the expression "too close for comfort"?
That--that was damn uncomfortable
What is it ? a resting house?
I didn't think anybody had those any more
They must be in there
Wow, it blends in nicely
OKoh, here we are
I -I see 'em
How many are there?
TwoI think
A man and a woman
Look out for the exit door
No door
no door there
still no door
no
Are you sure about that door ?
No no
What was that?
She's out of her mind!
Door! DOOR!
You're dead!
I'm here for the young woman
I wouldn't recommend it, dhampir
Taking on a vampire at night is a mission for morons and fools
which are you?
She's here by her own choice, dhampir
So unless you're the kind of man who would take a woman against her will for the money in it
and I'm sure it's a lot
I suggest you save your sorry ass now and leave us to travel in peace
I would if I could believe you, Meier
Your credibility, however, is less than impeccable under the circumstances
You kidnapped the girl
Meier!
Oh, my nose, my nose!
What happened ?
what'dwhat'd I miss?
She called out his name
It may be true, what he said
No, she's just ignorant
she's a child
She doesn't know him yet
She doesn't know what he's capable of
That poor girl
she'sshe's bleeding pretty bad
I mean, she won't last long
It's a shame
really -to waste all that good blood
I mean -come on, admit it -you're tempted
I mean, I know you are!
MMother
Wait, I was just kidding, y'know
C'mon, let's go
We got work to do
The money, c'mon; think of the money!
Hey, what did you do to me?
I bound your wound and stopped your bleeding That's all
Oh, I get it
You think you can just go ahead and tear off the clothes of whoever you come across
That's what you think, isn't it, DHAMPIR
You should go back home and nurse your wounds
What are you, my mother?
You called out for your mother before
I thought you might be needing her
Hey
I see her
When the last vampire is extinct, who will mourn our passing?
Will she? will anyone?
Can anyone understand this pain, this loneliness?
I told you so, didn't I?
I said, leave the girl alone
she's trouble
she's competition, y'know
YOU aided and abetted the enemy
I hope this is the right way
Trust me, I know how they think, these vampires:
when they're threatened, they all head for Barbarois
They're so predictable
Barbarois, yeah
And I really hate that place
It's full of lunatics and monsters, and that old crazy man, y'know
Does it hurt very much, Leila?
Leila?
Huh?
Your injurydoes it hurt you?
Oh, no, it's fine
I
Grove, you should lie down, you look tired
You need to restdon't worry about me
Leila
who dressed the wound? Was it him?
You can tell me
It was him, wasn't it? The dhampir hunter
Leila, I'm warning you
hehe's trouble He's against us
I don't know why he did that
Grove, please don't tell anyone, OK?
He stopped there
but what for?
Let's find out
Nolt and Kyle, you come with me
Leila, you stay in here with Grove
OKis everybody ready?
Always
Ready
Yeah
Hey, Nolt,  see what's goin' on in there, willya?
It may be a trap
Yeah, we'll cover you
It'll be my pleasure, gentlemen
It's nothin' but a lousy piece of cloth
What the hell ?
Bastardunbelievable!
Heywatch out!
So
you dare to enter Barbarois
I assume it's arrogance and vast stupidity that brings you here, gentlemen
or perhaps it's ignorance
You're skillful hunters, I can see
but you're no match for the Barbarois
Five thousand years of isolation have made us invincible!
Huh?
What?
What the hell's going on?
The shadow
watch out for the shadow
What're you talking about?
The shadowwhaddayou mean?
HeyNolt?
Hey, Nolt, what the hell happened to you, huh?
He'sHe's dead!
No, he's not!
Come on, Nolt
come on, snap out of it, come on
oh my God, damn it, come on!
I need you!
Oh GodNolt !
Oh, Godwe're getting close
Thoseare the windmills of the Barbarois
I really wish you'd turn back
There must be another way
There isn't
I am D, the hunter
I have business with the Barbarois
Oh, no
So I see you have dismounted
You have respect for your elders
That's very considerate indeed
I want you to stop your protection of Meier Link
You what?
You know, you make me laugh, that's a good one
I see you are a very humorous young man, and beautiful too, I might add
Or does that make you uncomfortable, to have an old lech like me admire you so?
Do you take me for a fool?
Someone paid me a hundred million dollars to protect Meier Link
Can you top that?
Well, you drive a hard bargain there, old man
what if I can?
You really are entertaining me, Mr Stranger!
I suppose you know our reputation
the Barbarois serve the people of the night,
and after five thousand years, I don't think we're about to change our stripes anytime soon,
although if we did for anyone it would be for you
I have seen many a dhampir,
but somebody like you I've never seen before
That's why it's such a pity that you have to die
I really can't let you leave here alive, now, can I?
I'm afraid you have to die, Stranger
So sorry
The Barbarois are great warriors
You are a warrior too, no doubt
and although you may kill some of us,
in the end we will prevail
I have sworn to protect the carriage
prepare to die!
Fool!
What's he doin' in there?
Borgoff, are we ready yet?
Grove
we have no choice
We need your help on this, Grove
Think you can do it there, man?
Give it to me
I'm waiting
Don't push yourself too hard, now
I mean it, OK
I want you back
You know, I really have nothing against the Barbarois personally
It's a shame I'll have to kill so many of you
Indeed, I admire your loyalty and your devotion to duty
Yet I wonder about the fairness when you allow one to fight against so many
But
if that will entertain you
I see
you make I see a good argument, young man
how interesting
Oh, man, I think the fellow is right
Please allow the three of us to entertain our young guest here,
unless he thinks that's unfair
three against one, how unfair, three against one, unfair
That's enough!
You mock us with your ridiculous antics, Benge
I will not have you distracting us from the job at hand, which is the protection of the carriage
We'll do things my wayhuh?
What the devil is that?
Go for it, Grovego for it!
Kill all those guys
kill every last one of 'em!
Come on, Grove, hold on
Get the carriage out now!
Follow me, Tinkerbell
I'm waiting for you!
Grove!
I've got to say this
I admire that young hunter's spirit,
although he doesn't stand a chance against Benge and the others
Still, it's a pity I'll miss the show
Oh well, c'est la vie
Wake up, D!
What's wrong with you?
It's not fair, it's not fair
I'll show you what's not fair!
Stay there till you rot, hunter!
Suckers!
Stop, I beg you
Say goodnight
Kyle, did you happen to see where that girl went?
Maybe she got caught in the wheels
Go look
Nice, Caroline, very nice
A little crude, but effective
They're all yours!
That freakin' monster
Is everybody all right?
Yeah, but Kyle was outside
He was up on top
Kyle?
Kyle, where the hell are you, Kyle?
Down here!
You OK?
Quiet! They're still around!
No!
Damn! That idiot!
Well, how convenient this is for me
Come on out here so I can finish the job
Your time is up
Come on, you coward!
You're gonna pay for the pain you caused my brother
D! Are you awake?
I need your help to swallow up this spell
You're a slave driver, you know that?
Hey, remember to watch out for the shadow, huh?
Try and stay still
Easier said than done
And keep your mouth shut
That was close
Well, the tank is fulla holes
Fuel's all gone, we can't drive it like this anyway
What're we gonna do?
What Should We Do?
Borgoff, any idea?
How's Grove?
Honestly, not too great
Borgoff, wake up!
What are you thinking about over there?
Oh, nothin', really
I was just thinkin' about the carriage
Wonder where it is by now
Well, man, at this point it's pretty much anybody's guess
If you want my opinion, I'd say they're either setting sail from the port of Abrol or hiding somewhere deep in the Grenerge Mountain Range
I sure hope so
Anyway, we still have to get some fuel
and the town of Garucia isn't that far away from here
Kyle, you go with Leila
I'll stay here and do the repairs
If you are seeking the pathway to the stars, come to me
I pray for your safe arrival with all my heart
The pathway to the stars
I dunno about you, but y'know, I sure miss that horse
What was his name?
Ohoh, the silent treatment, huh?
Well, I got two words for you: Heat syndrome
Look -look, I know I'm a parasite, but haven't I always been a helpful parasite?
You may not care if you die from heat
but becoming a piece of beef jerky is not a lifelong ambition of mine
Yeah, well, what's the sound of one hand yapping
How much?
Oh no -keep your money
C'mon, just take it --
Let's go
Leila?
Oh I see
It's him, isn't it?
Kyle, why don't you start back without me
There's something I want to do here first
Back off
Have I told you
you're quite irresistible in that sexy skin-tight getup?
No -tell me about it
I just did
Make sure you watch your back with that guy, Leila
I'd like a beer
I've just been admirin' your fancy weapon there
Don't worry
I have no plans to use it anytime soon
That's good
That's good, 'cause I have no plans to let you keep it
Give it up
You heard me, little girl
Mm Thank you
Well, here's to ya, Sheriff
I'd buy you a drink, but
Thank you, but no thanks
Oh, OK I was just gonna say, you must be awfully busy with that new dhampir hunter in the town now
What dhampir hunter?
I'd like to buy that horse
Three hundred thousand dollars
And if you don't like the price, go somewhere else
Freeze! Put your hands where I can see 'em Now!
Sheriff, he paid good money for that
What are you doing?!
Take your money and go
We don't want you here
We don't sell to dhampirs in this town, understand?
Understand me, dhampir?
You understand
Wait a minute That's my horse you're talking about there,
and I'll sell it to whoever I want if they can afford the price I'm asking
You can't do that
We have laws against it, Polkgood laws, and for a damn good reason
What laws?
Don't play coy, Polk, you know as well as I dhampirs aren't allowed
Not allowed, right
I remember a time not that long ago when we had vampires and dhampirs both around here But
And that's why we have the law
Listen to me, whether you want to hear it or notyou weren't even born when this happened
Do yourself a favor and listen to the story
I'm going to tell you about the time when the children were kidnapped
There were ten children altogether
Yeah, I heard about that time
The kidnappers turned out to be vampires, of course
And so the townspeople pooled their money to hire a vampire hunter
They wanted the best
And when the hunter came
he was a very strong and quiet man
and he did his job, too, which was to return the children safely back into their parents' homes
It wasn't easy, but many vampires died by his hands before this job was over with
And when it was over and the children were back home,
the people attacked the man
They said he was a dhampir, half vampire himselfso they punished him
Can't say I blame them for doing that
You can't trust 'em, that's all that's about
They were right about that part, Polk
He did the job!
I see then, I'll have to take matters into my own hands
Let him go
What is that?
What does it look like, idiot?
Put down your guns
Polk, you can't know what you're doing put it down
I know exactly what I'm doing
You DON'T know! Put it down now, you old fool!
I would much rather be an old fool than what you are, Sheriff
Now, don't shoot
I can tell you I won't think twice about using this weapon
I might even enjoy it
Get on your horse, Stranger
Thank you
No, it's only fitting I thank you
It's the least I can do
I may be just an old fool now, Stranger,  but I could never forget a face like yours
And I'll never forget what you done for me back then
That's rightI was one of them kids
And I always felt bad about that
the way you was treated
How nobody stopped you, nobody thanked you instead the ignorant bastards ran you right out of our town
So it's true, isn't it, what they say about you dhampirs
You don't age
Now goI'm getting tired
Where's Benge? What's taking him so long?
Well, the horses are rested now We'd better go
Come on
Master, what is it? May I help you, sir?
It's still light outside, Master!
What?
Leave her alone, Mashira
Yes, sir
She misses the sunlight Let her enjoy it
I am D, the hunter
Your father sent me
Don't be afraidI won't hurt you
You sit in the sunlightyou must not be changed
So why do you stay with him?
Last night in the carriage you called out his name
Why did you call for him?
I suppose my father has not told you that I'm in love with Meier
You don't know who he is
You can't be in love with him
Well, I am
If you only knew how good he's been to me
I love him
Please believe me; no one else will
You don't understand
He is what he is, Charlotte
You can't change him; he'll take you in time
And when that happens, I will have to kill you
Fine; kill me, then
I would rather die than to go anywhere without him
Don't take me back thereI mean it I simply could not live without Meier
How sweet that is
She loves a vampire
So very sweet
Idiot!
You stupid girl, get up! We're going
Leave me alone!
You'll do what I say
Do you have any idea how many people have died at the hands of your beloved Meier, this vampire you wanna protect!
None!
You fool! And youYou stay right where you are, my friend
Sorry, but I really don't want to have to share any of my profits
You understand, don't youit's business
Above you
What's wrong? Tell me!
Too much sun
I warned you about the heat, but you don't listen!
Come on You can't survive unless you dig a hole You need to bury yourself!
Hurry!
Leila! Leila, are you there? Come in, Leila
Yeah, I copy
Thank God Are you OK? What's your position?
I'm near Lake Chiffon Our game is heading north from here
We'll catch up
Leila, do you know what's happened to the dhampir hunter?
No; I haven't seen him
All right Well, take care
Stay in touch Borgoff out
The tables have turned
Now, that cleared my head
I really should return the favor, don't you think, honey?
Don't get any ideas
Hey, I'm just trying to stay dry here
If there was any other place to go, believe me, I'd be there
As soon as the rain lets up, I'll be gone from here and from you
I think I can guess your problem
Your family was the victim of vampires
You don't know what you're talking about
You don't know anything about it
All right Perhaps I don't
This stupid thingit bothers me
You really are a weird one, you know that?
In spite of being a dhampir hunter and all that that entails
How did you know about my mother?
You called her name, remember?
She was kidnapped by vampires
My father went after her and was trying to rescue her so they killed him
And after a while my mother returned, but she wasn't my mother any more
she'd been changed
The people in the village stoned her to death while I watched
After that I left home
I met the Markus brothers and joined with them
I wanted to be a hunter to avenge my parents' deaths
I've seen many terrible things since then, lives destroyed, families devastated, hopes crushed
every time, it seems vampire is to blame
I can understand why you'd choose to do it, but the life of a hunter is no kind of life
It's the only life I'm any good for now, and it looks like it's the only life you've ever known
So I suggest we make a pact
Since we're both in it for the long haul, whoever dies first, the other one can come and bring flowers to their grave
How's that?
It's the rain
makes me sentimental
I don't know why I should care about thatit's just I love flowers
And I don't think I'll be getting any
I'm all alone, after all
We have that much in common, don't we
That we're both hunters and we're both alone
Oh well, I'm being sillydoesn't really matter
I'll do it
I'll bring you flowers if I survive thisbut I don't expect to
Stop, I didn't really mean it when I said that
And anyway, I don't really understand why you should keep on doing this
Because I'm a dhampir
I don't get to have a life; not like you
Well, with the rainstorm last night, they can't be too far away
We're even now, dhampirunderstand?
I have a very bad feeling about this
How so?
I think I've finally figured it out, Borgoff
Well, I'm sure you're rightif you're thinking they're headed for the castle
Yeah, that's right, the castlethe Castle of Chaythe!
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING, WE CAN'T GO IN THERE, IT WOULD BE SUICIDE!
What are you now, afraid of a little insanity?
Since when have we been sane?
We just have to get to them before they reach the castle
There's a bridge up aheadthat's where we intercept the carriage
I remember that trick from the time we got those vampires at Keldo
Yeah, it worked that time, and it can work again now
Leila, come in; come in, Leila Over
Yeah it's me, I copy
What's up?
I'm on my way
Don't move
I'm warning youtry anything funny and you'll be blown to smithereens
You wanna try it?
I didn't think so
We just want the girl
Hello there!
She's still human!
Come on, get out of there NOW!
Borgoff, she won't come
We're doing you a favor!
Come ON, I said get outta there!
Let that be a lesson to ya, you cowardly Barbarois animal
Borgoff, look
Borgoff!
What? What the --?
What, is this guy crazy?
Doesn't he know he can't exist outside here in the sunlight?
I won't let you take her!
Oh, yeah?
Thanks a lotyou're making our job a lot easier
Hot enough for ya?
What you deserve!
Over here, hot stuff!
Oohoo, lookit him burn!
No!
What the hell do you want
How's that feelmoron!
lookit him!
Hey, where do you think!
Why'd you let her go!
I love you
I can't go on without you
What?
Borgoff, we should just let her kill herself
and then we can finish him off, what do you think about that idea?
We get the money if she's dead or alive
Hey, you're rightOK
Stop it!
Kyle!
I'll blow you to hell!
What!
I don't want you to worry about these wounds of mine
They will heal
Then we shall go to the city of night and distant stars
When we go there we can be alone and free to love each other
It's true, believe me; we'll be there soon
We're it now; we're the only ones left, Borgoff; we should just give it up
If we make it into that castle, none of us will make it out alive
We CAN'T quit now
We owe it to Kyle and to Nolt to keep going on
Listen, Borgoff
Shaddup! I won't hear it
Leilawhat do you think?
Grove, they fear us
They fear us because they know our reputation That we never give up
And we never can
If we quit now, we might as well quit the business, and I can't do that
I won't do ittill every last one of them is gone
Masterdo you hear?
He is coming
The castle is nearby
I'll stay here and deal with him
Getting close The Castle of Chaythe
Soon we'll be able to see it
the home of Carmila, the Bloody Countess
You've heard of her
For five thousand years her rule of terror lasted, and then, that was that!
Your father, the vampire king, grew angry
He was impatient with her vanity; offended by her bloodlust, her gluttony
He grew so tired that he killed her while she slept, impaling her on a sword, and that was it for her
Except she haunts the place now with phantoms and demons, but you don't care about that, do you?
But I bet I know what really gets to you, dhampir
what REALLY gets to you
the thought of those two lovebirds giving birth to another dhampir, huh?
That's it
You see, I know you; I know how you think, I know how you feel, I know every move that you make, you can't
I'm glad we could meet at last, Hunter D
You are a worthy opponent
Who hired the Barbarois?
Who were you working for?
It was Carmila who hired us
And as a Barbarois, my duty has been fulfilled
Now I can die in peace
I gather from your letter that you had a rather difficult time
I think I can understand what it's like
Love is not unique to humans, you know
we vampires are very susceptible
I hope I can be of service
We're very grateful, Carmila
You both must be exhausted
Perhaps you should rest first
I'm sure that the young lady would like to freshen up
You've probably heard rumors about me, but I can assure you, they all stem from jealousy and envy
I'm not the "Bloody Carmila" they like to portray me as
Now, behold
That's it; that is the ship
It will take you to the city of the night where you can live peacefully at last
You can be happy there
There was a time, many years ago, when every castle had a ship like this one and the night sky was full of their flashing lights
Those were the days when vampires flourished and a love like yours was not so desperately impossible
So different from today
Our numbers dwindling, hunted and alone, we're hopelessly misunderstood
but you two seem to have beaten the odds
I'm very very happy for you
The ship hasn't been used in years
I've no idea if it will fly safely, but I'm sure that's a risk you're prepared to take
We're very grateful
I only wish I could go with you
You look so beautiful
Why stop? I want you, Meier I want all of you
Why not?
You don't know what it's like, Charlotte
to live forever in darkness eternal, forever thirsting for blood despite your best intention
I can't imagine that life for you; not for you, Charlotte
You're so selfish, Meier
I carry a heavy weight on my conscience
Those villagers and the bounty hunter and my familythey still mourn my loss, Meier
It wasn't your doing, Charlotte
It was my fault entirely
Well, then we're both to blame, because we can't know happiness; not anymore
I wanted you to be happy, Meier, and so I abandoned my father and my brother for you
But their pain set the wheels in motion for our pain, and so on and on it goes
All we have is each other now, and I want to be close to you
Without that we have nothing
All the pain I've caused and all the agony I feel is nothing now!
And you are everything to me, my love
We'll talk more on our trip to the stars, if that's all right with you
There is some unfinished business I have to attend to
Do not leave this room, understand?
D
Listen, Meier The woman says she wants to go back home
I don't believe it
Charlotte
I dunno, something's not right
'Course, ah, you don't have to take my word for it
you can judge for yourself
Let's go!
Leila, don't go
Leila, don't go in there
If you go in there, you're never coming back!
Oh, I'm coming back
No!
Leila, check upstairs
I'm on it
Nice hat
I know you hate me, D
Please try and understand
I loved your father
What choice did I have?
Nolt, Kyle
hey, I don't believe it!
You two sure are a sight for sore eyes!
What are you doing? Get up!
Why aren't you listeningI said get up!
Go away
Get out of here!
Can you forgive me, D?
D?
I know it's been lonely for you
I was lonely too
until you came along
Did you hear? D?
It's OK, honey
it's OK to cry
I know I know how you feel
It wasn't your fault It wasn't
Yes it was!
Let go!
It's just an illusion
Carmila's playing with us
Excellentwhat fun!
I haven't had this much fun in centuries!
You don't mind, do you?
It just makes things so much more interesting
You're doing very well, by the way very well indeed
The womanwhere are you hiding her?
Borgoffwhat are you doing! We don't have time for this!
Leila -are you in love with this dhampir?
Are you crazy? What is wrong with you
Borgoff!
Dhampir
drop your weapon
Drop it now!
She took you in, didn't she?
She'll die! I'm warning you, dhampir, don't come any closer
Enough! Now you die
Grove!
Grove, no!
Lei la
Lookshe's comingCarmila
The spirit of Carmila!
Dhampir hunteryour mother was human, but your father was a vampire, and you're betraying his ancient blood
You side with humans against us
Your people are facing extinction, and you're contributing to their demise
You stalk and kill your own ancestors, dhampir
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED!
Your human self is your weaker self
Humans are nothing more than livestock
We prey on them as they prey on beasts
This is the rule of nature!
Your time is coming to an end
Your kind must face extinction
You cannot survive; you must die
That is the rule of nature
Ahvery strong words for a dhampir
But you seem to forgetour spirits are eternal
No, Carmila; nothing lasts forever
I see
I should have known better than to reason with your kind, dhampir hunter
I guess my only option is to use force
Nothis can't happen!
Are you the son of the vampire king?
Who are you? Who are you, dhampir?
Such power!
Charlotte, come back I need you; please come back
Darling, is that you?
Oh yes It's meMeier
I'm so happy, Meier, because we are together now At last
Together At last
You made me happy, Meier
You let me dream You let me dream of our beautiful trip to the stars
Our dream
Our beautiful, wonderful dream
It's not a dream We are going to those stars, Charlotte
Oh, my dear one
You and I will get away from here
We will fly together to the city of the night where we were meant to be free from all of this
where you can rest, my love, finally, and be free
Yesfreedom! At last
My precious, precious love
Let's goaway from here
Stop right there, Meier
I'm taking her backback to her family who loved her
She knew I loved her best of all
You can't understand it You've never loved a human
I've never killed one, either
You struggle to resist this nature of ours, but it can't last forever, D
The urge for their blood is stronger
If that day comes, then another will hunt me
It's as simple as that
What a waste What a sad waste
Enough of killing Enough of misery and death
I've had enough
I've had enough!
Why did you miss my heart?
She's dead The ring is all I need
I'll take it to her father
As proof
Mind giving me a ride just as far as the next town?
I'd appreciate it
That reward money would rightfully be mine, y'know
But hey, I'm generous
I'll let you keep it just this one time
Where is he taking her?
Away from here
Away
Fly, COME ON!
You can make it
come on!
Fly away
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here in this resting place to bid farewell to our sister
Into your gentle arms we commend her gracious spirit
Take her to yourself and give her safe haven
And though she struggled in life, now she knows your blessed peace
For all who question will find answers,
and all who love will find contentment, joy, and peace eternal
For now we see as through a glass darkly,
but then we shall see clearly, face to face
Mister!
Wait!
Mister, WAIT!
excuse me, sir, butI was wondering if you knew my grandmother Leila
Yes it's you, isn't it
My grandmother told me about you,
soI'd be honored if you'd come to our house, my dad would be so happy
please?
I appreciate your kindness
Oh, c'mon We don't live very far
I just came here to keep a promise to an old friend of mine
She was afraid no one would mourn her death
I'm glad she was so wrong
Huh?
OK, I guess I see
Anyway, thank you for coming, sir
G'bye!
G-bye!!
Well, that was nice
You're not so bad after all
You just dress bad
Subtitles y Mhmm m