Who?
Who are you?
Angel's Egg.
Keep precious things inside you...
...or you will lose them.
What do you think is
inside that egg?
I can't tell you things like that.
Besides, I don't even know
who you are.
You have to break an egg
if you are to know what is inside.
Who are you?
Don't follow mel.
The fish have come out.
Fish?
Even though the fish
are not anywhere...
...still they chase after them.
Please...
...my egg...
...don't do anything to it.
This way.
I've seen a tree
like this somewhere.
Where was it?
So long ago that I've forgotten.
Somewhere under a sky where the clouds
made sounds as they moved.
The black horizon swelled
and from it grew a huge tree.
It sucked the life
from the ground
and its pulsing branches
reached up,
as if to grasp something.
The giant bird sleeping
within an egg.
What happened to the bird?
Where is it?
It's still there now,
still dreaming.
Dreaming?
What kind of dream
does the bird dream?
What is in the egg?
You still cannot tell me?
Since when have you
been here?
As many days as there
are bottles?
I too have forgotten
where I'm from.
And maybe, I didn't know from
the beginning where I am going.
Will you be going away?
I will wipe from the earth man
whom I have created...
...man and beast, crawling creature
and bird of the air as well...
...for I regret that I made them.
I will send rain on the earth
for forty days and forty nights...
...and I will wipe from the ground
every living thing I have made.
And after seven days the waters
of the flood came upon the earth.
On that very day all the fountains
of the great deep burst forth...
...and the floodgates of
the heavens were opened.
And rain fell on the earth
forty days and forty nights.
But the ark floated on
the surface of the waters.
All flesh that moved on
the earth died...
...birds, cattle, wild animals, all creatures
that creep on the earth, and all men.
Only Noah and those with him
in the ark were left.
Then he sent a dove to see if the waters
had abated from the surface of the ground.
Then he waited another seven days, and
again sent forth the dove from the ark...
...but she did not return
to him any more.
Where did the bird land?
Or maybe it weakened
and was swallowed by the waters.
No one could know.
So the people waited
for her return.
Waited and grew tired of waiting.
They forgot they had released the bird;
Forgot there was a bird.
They even forgot there was
a world sunken under water.
They forgot where they were from; How long
they traveled; And where they were going.
It was so long ago that
the animals have turned to stone.
The bird I saw, I can't even remember
where or when, it was so long ago.
Perhaps it was a dream.
Maybe you and I and the fish exist only in
the memory of a person who is gone.
Maybe no one really exists
and it is only raining outside.
Maybe the bird never existed at all.
It exists.
It's here.
I found it, it's already
turned to stone, it's in here.
I'm going to hatch it and put it back.
It's the bird I found.
I know that.
I thought so.
Can you hear something?
I can hear it.
The sound of soft breathing.
That's your breathing.
I can hear the sound of wings.
It must be dreaming of flying in the sky.
That's just the sound of
the wind outside.
Very soon. That's just the
sound of the wind outside.
Very soon.
Right now you're in here dreaming,
but soon I will show you.
Very soon.
So you must stay here for now.
Here it doesn't rain...
Here it is warm.
Who are you?
Who?